Live Web Evidence Agent is built for a common failure in AI research: confident answers with weak traceability.
Teams need to know which claims came from which source, what is current, and which sentences should not be repeated yet.
For DeveloperWeek New York, this targets the Nimble live web challenge with source cards, a claim ledger, blocked claims, a voice handoff gate, and an approval-ready answer.
The app loads a dated public-page snapshot. A sponsor-backed version can feed the same table with live search, extract, crawl, or agent results.
The source cards show where the evidence came from, so the answer cannot float away from its sources.
The claim ledger gives each claim a source, confidence level, and decision.
Blocked claims tell the user what not to repeat until sources and sponsor integrations are verified.
The voice handoff gate prepares a resume packet and can call a human back only when judgment is required.
The approval-ready answer turns the ledger into a usable response without hiding uncertainty.
The product is live web speed, source discipline, and an AI agent that keeps working until human judgment is truly needed.